Treasure] Radio, iNews extra edition
Thank you very much.
Now, in this video, we're going to do an extension of the Delusional Phrase Championship.
We'll be doing an extended version of the Delusional Phrase Championship.
We've had some requests from our listeners, so we've decided to do this.
Sora won!
Sora won. [Treasure] I won. [Treasure] So, please choose your team. [Moa] I'll take the lead.
I'll let you choose. -I'm going to do it. -She's strong. -Go ahead of me.
I see. And now, for our situation, we're on our way home from school.
You're going to ask a classmate you're interested in to go home with you.
I'd love to hear it. -Okay, then. -Okay.
It's okay. The phrase championship is about to begin. Hey, Kuribayashi... you live close to me, don't you?
I remembered to drink tea yesterday, but I forgot today.
I forgot what I didn't remember today, so I want to go home with you.
You want to go home together? I want to go home with you.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Mr. Suzuki is smiling.
I didn't think you'd want to go home with me.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Mr. Suzuki, I'll let you be the judge, but please wait a moment.
Not yet.
Sora, on the other hand...
I'd like you to do something for me.
What is it?
I want you to say bye-bye first.
Okay.
And if I'm flustered...
Yeah.
I'll say bye-bye first, and then if I'm flustered, you'll say bye-bye, and then if I say bye-bye like, "What do you mean?
Okay, well, I guess that's the plan, so let's start the Delusional Phrase Championship.
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
I think you should take it off. I think you should take it off.
Also... today's assignment for English class... is it on page 34?
And what did the teacher say on the way home? What do you want to say?
I want to be with you a little longer, so I'm talking to you again.
I mean, I want to go home with you.
Let's go home.
Cute!
What's this?
Mr. Suzuki, you've been listening to this with a smile on your face.
I'd like you to judge.
I don't want to be judged.
Hey...
You're...
You're cute with everyone.
What do you think?
I think you're cute.
Moa-chan's got a great personality, but... she can't do her job.
Sora, you're amazing... and you could be an actress right now.
Well, the result is... they both win.
Both win! It's really wonderful!
But, as you can see, this kind of expressive power is being used more and more in the performance.
Well, I'm sure you'll be going to live events soon.
Will you go?
I'm sure you'll go to the event sometime.